[
    {
        "question": "It is not always easy to ............ new friends.",
        "choices": [
            "do",
            "look",
            "spend",
            "make"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "make"
    },
    {
        "question": "Some students try to ............ a job during the summer holidays.",
        "choices": [
            "go",
            "do",
            "get",
            "leave"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "get"
    },
    {
        "question": "Vegetables ............ a lot of health benefits if eaten fresh.",
        "choices": [
            "donate",
            "have",
            "check",
            "pay"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "have"
    },
    {
        "question": "I admire your idea. In this sentence, 'admire' is an antonym of ............ .",
        "choices": [
            "praise",
            "approve of",
            "disapprove of",
            "appreciate"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "disapprove of"
    },
    {
        "question": "\"She's a long-term illness.\" \"Long-term\" here means ............ .",
        "choices": [
            "serious",
            "temporary",
            "short",
            "simple"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "serious"
    },
    {
        "question": "\"He donated some blood.\" The word 'donated' can be replaced by ............ .",
        "choices": [
            "received",
            "gave",
            "kept",
            "a & c"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "gave"
    },
    {
        "question": "\"I know you are generous.\" 'Generous' here is antonymous with ............ .",
        "choices": [
            "helpful",
            "selfish",
            "mean",
            "b & c"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "selfish"
    },
    {
        "question": "\"Donate\" is to 'receive' as ............ is to stupidity.",
        "choices": [
            "intelligence",
            "intelligent",
            "domestic",
            "tame"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "intelligence"
    },
    {
        "question": "I can't help my ............ for your mentality.",
        "choices": [
            "admire",
            "admirer",
            "admiration",
            "admired"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "admiration"
    },
    {
        "question": "I really ............ your mentality.",
        "choices": [
            "admire",
            "admirer",
            "admiration",
            "admired"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "admire"
    },
    {
        "question": "First, a blood ............ has to be checked carefully to make sure they are healthy.",
        "choices": [
            "donate",
            "donor",
            "donation",
            "donated"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "donation"
    },
    {
        "question": "First, you need to be checked carefully before you ............ blood to make sure you are healthy.",
        "choices": [
            "donate",
            "donor",
            "donation",
            "donated"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "donate"
    },
    {
        "question": "............ blood is synonymous with giving it.",
        "choices": [
            "Transplanting",
            "Transfusing",
            "Pressuring",
            "Donating"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "Donating"
    },
    {
        "question": "He ............ to live in a large villa in a coastal town.",
        "choices": [
            "desire",
            "desires",
            "desiring",
            "is desiring"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "desires"
    },
    {
        "question": "His ............ is to live in a large villa in a coastal town.",
        "choices": [
            "desire",
            "desires",
            "desiring",
            "is desiring"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "desire"
    },
    {
        "question": "What makes people admire him more is his ............ .",
        "choices": [
            "genre",
            "generous",
            "generosity",
            "generously"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "genre"
    },
    {
        "question": "What makes people admire him more is the fact that he is . . . . . . . . . . . . . generous.",
        "choices": [
            "genre",
            "generous",
            "generosity",
            "generously"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "generosity"
    },
    {
        "question": "He won't take ............ the race as he is injured.",
        "choices": [
            "place",
            "care of",
            "part in",
            "turns"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "part in"
    },
    {
        "question": "My father praised me ............ helping the poor old man.",
        "choices": [
            "for",
            "of",
            "with",
            "to"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "for"
    },
    {
        "question": "When I was talking with her for the first time, I found ............ that she is intelligent.",
        "choices": [
            "in",
            "out about",
            "out",
            "b & c"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "b & c"
    },
    {
        "question": "In his ............, Taha Hussein wrote about all that happened to him in his life.",
        "choices": [
            "graphy",
            "autobiography",
            "biography",
            "geography"
        ],
        "correct_answer": "autobiography"
    }
]